A Guide to the Trust for Mutual Understanding records FA412
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants, 1970, 1975, 1978, 1982, 1987-2012; 3; 45.95 Cubic Feet 121 letter document boxes
  - New Haven International Festival of Arts & Ideas, EC-0705, 2006-2007 (Box 101, Folder 1114)
  - New Haven International Festival of Arts & Ideas, Miscellaneous, EC-0705, 2004-2009 (Box 101, Folder 1115-1116)
  - New Haven International Festival of Arts & Ideas, B-0870, 2008-2009 (Box 101, Folder 1117)
  - New Haven International Festival of Arts & Ideas, EC-0802, 2007-2008 (Box 102, Folder 1118)
  - New Mexico State University, EC-0327, 2003-2004, 2006 (Box 102, Folder 1119)
  - New Mexico State University, DF-0504, 2004-2006 (Box 102, Folder 1120)
  - New Radio and Performing Arts, B-0828, 2008 (Box 102, Folder 1121)
  - The New Wilderness Foundation, DF-0417, 2004-2005 (Box 102, Folder 1122)
  - New York Botanical Garden, B-0228, 2001-2003 (Box 102, Folder 1123)
  - New York City Ballet, B-0366, DF-0402, 2003-2004, 2006-2007 (Box 102, Folder 1124)
  - New York City Ballet, Miscellaneous, B-0366, 2003-2004 (Box 102, Folder 1125)
  - New York Foundation for the Arts (NYFA), Louise Bourgeois, B-0156, 2000-2003, 2006 (Box 102, Folder 1126)
  - New York Foundation for the Arts (NYFA), B-0465, 1987-1988, 2000-2006 (Box 102, Folder 1127)
  - New York Foundation for the Arts (NYFA), DF-0544, 2005-2009 (Box 103, Folder 1128)
  - New York Foundation for the Arts (NYFA), Seagull Films, B-0666, 2000-2004, 2006-2008 (Box 103, Folder 1129)
  - New York International Ballet Competition, DF-0332, 2003, 2006 (Box 103, Folder 1130)
  - New York Landmarks Conservancy, DF-0435, 2004-2005 (Box 103, Folder 1131)
  - New York Public Library (NYPL), EC-0205, 2001-2004 (Box 103, Folder 1132)
  - New York Public Library (NYPL), DF-0703, 2005-2007 (Box 103, Folder 1133)
  - New York Public Library (NYPL), DF-0703, New York Public Library, "Beyond Russia Imagined" Photos (Box 103, Folder 1133)
  - New York Public Library (NYPL), DF-0828, 2007-2009 (Box 103, Folder 1134)
  - New York Public Library (NYPL), DF-0828, Revolutionary Voices: Performing Arts in Central & Eastern Europe in the 1980s, The New York Public Library for the Performing Arts, 2009 November 18-2010 March 20 (Box 103, Folder 1134)
  - New York Public Library (NYPL), Performing Revolution, DF-0828, 2010 (Box 103, Folder 1135)
  - New York Theatre Workshop, DF-0136, 2001-2002, 2006 (Box 103, Folder 1136)
  - New York Theatre Workshop, B-0517, 2002-2006 (Box 103, Folder 1137)
  - New York Theatre Workshop, B-0627, 2004-2008 (Box 103, Folder 1138)
  - New York University (NYU), B-0563, 2002-2003, 2005-2008 (Box 104, Folder 1139)
  - New York University (NYU), B-0563, New York University, Photographs from the Prague Symposium "Education and Training for the Conservation of Photographic Maters in Eastern Europe", 2005 June 21-23 (Box 104, Folder 1139)
  - New York University (NYU) Museum Studies Program, DF-0203, 2001-2003, 2006, 2009 (Box 104, Folder 1140)
  - New York University (NYU) School of Law, B-0429, 2003-2005, 2007-2008 (Box 104, Folder 1141)
  - New York University (NYU) School of Law, Miscellaneous, B-0429, 2001 (Box 104, Folder 1142)
  - New York University (NYU) Tisch School of the Arts, B-0871, 2008-2010 (Box 104, Folder 1143)
  - Nine Circles Chamber Theatre, EC-0206, 2002, 2004, 2006-2007 (Box 104, Folder 1144)
  - Nonprofit Enterprise and Self-Sustainability Team (NESsT), B-0642, 2005-2008 (Box 104, Folder 1145)
  - Northeast Document Conservation Center (NEDCC), Bratislava, B-0135, 2000-2003 (Box 104, Folder 1146)
  - Northeast Document Conservation Center (NEDCC), B-0222, 2001-2003 (Box 104, Folder 1147)
  - Northeast Document Conservation Center (NEDCC), Bratislava, B-0252, 2002-2004 (Box 104, Folder 1148)
  - Northeast Document Conservation Center (NEDCC), B-0292, 2001-2004 (Box 105, Folder 1149)
  - Northeast Document Conservation Center (NEDCC), B-0292 (Box 105, Folder 1149)
  - Northeast Document Conservation Center (NEDCC), DF-0209, 2001-2003 (Box 105, Folder 1150)
  - Northeast Document Conservation Center (NEDCC), Workshop on Photo Conservation,B-0324, 2002-2004 (Box 105, Folder 1151)
  - Northeast Document Conservation Center (NEDCC), B-0367, 2003-2004 (Box 105, Folder 1152)
  - Northeast Document Conservation Center (NEDCC), Photographs, 2003-2004 (Box 105, Folder 1153)
  - Northeast Document Conservation Center (NEDCC), B-0425, 2003-2005 (Box 105, Folder 1154)
  - Northeast Document Conservation Center (NEDCC), Summer Institute on Photo Conservation, B-0466, 2004-2006 (Box 105, Folder 1155)
  - Northeast Document Conservation Center (NEDCC), Summer Institute on Photo Conservation, Miscellaneous, B-0466 (Box 105, Folder 1156)
  - Northeast Document Conservation Center (NEDCC), Conservation Faculty Exchanges, B-0467, 2004-2006 (Box 105, Folder 1157)
  - Northeast Document Conservation Center (NEDCC), B-0564, 2004-2008 (Box 106, Folder 1158)
  - Northeast Document Conservation Center (NEDCC), Miscellaneous, B-0564, 2006-2007 (Box 106, Folder 1159)
  - Northeast Document Conservation Center (NEDCC), DF-0520, 2002-2006 (Box 106, Folder 1160)
  - Northeast Document Conservation Center Misc., DF-0520 (Box 106, Folder 1161)
  - Northeast Document Conservation Center (NEDCC), B-0766, 2006-2009 (Box 106, Folder 1162)
  - Northeast Document Conservation Center (NEDCC), Miscellaneous, B-0766, 2008-2009 (Box 106, Folder 1163)
  - Northeast Document Conservation Center (NEDCC), Miscellaneous, B-0766, Karol Weisscher, 2006 (Box 106, Folder 1163)
    Separated Materials
    Special format items (audio, film, video, digital media, library materials, memorabilia, oversize, and photographic material) have been separated from the file and assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
  - Northeast Document Conservation Center (NEDCC), Miscellaneous, B-0766, NEDCC, Photographs, NEDCC's Photograph Conservation Training Program for Eastern and Central Europeans, 2008 (Box 106, Folder 1163)
  - Northern Forum, B-0233, 2001-2003 (Box 106, Folder 1164)
  - Northern Forum, B-0475, 2004-2006 (Box 107, Folder 1165)
  - Northern Forum, B-0475, Northern Forum, Brown Bear Working Group, 5th Workshop, Hokkaido, Japan, 2005 August 6-13 (Box 107, Folder 1165)
  - Northern Forum, Flood Working Group, B-0674, 2006-2008 (Box 107, Folder 1166)
  - Northern Forum, Flood Working Group, Miscellaneous, B-0674, 2007 (Box 107, Folder 1167)
  - Northern Forum, DF-0608, 2005-2006 (Box 107, Folder 1168)
  - Northern Forum, DF-0608, Northern Forum Flood Workshop, 3rd Workshop, Yakutsk, Russia, 2006 May 9-12 (Box 107, Folder 1168)
  - Northern Forum, 6th Brown Bear Working Group, B-0744, 2006-2007 (Box 107, Folder 1169)
  - Northern Forum, 6th Brown Bear Working Group, B-0744, Northern Forum, Photos, 2007 Flood Work Group, 2007 Brown Bear, 2007 Cultural Festival (Box 107, Folder 1169)
  - Northern Forum, Pamuya to "Northern Cultural Festival", DF-0721, 2006-2008 (Box 107, Folder 1170)
  - Nuclear Information and Resource Service, B-0173, 2001-2002 (Box 107, Folder 1171)
  - Nuclear Information and Resource Service, B-0534, 2001, 2004-2005, 2008 (Box 107, Folder 1172)
  - Nuclear Information and Resource Service, EC-0608, 2005-2008 (Box 107, Folder 1173)
  - NURTUREart, DF-0416, 2003-2007 (Box 107, Folder 1174)
  - NURTUREart, Miscellaneous, DF-0416, 2007 (Box 107, Folder 1175)
  - OhioDance, B-0426, 2004, 2007 (Box 107, Folder 1176)
  - OhioDance, B-0565, 2005-2009 (Box 108, Folder 1177)
  - OhioDance, EC-0502, 2004-2005, 2007-2009 (Box 108, Folder 1178)
  - OhioDance, XII Annual Conference, Festival in Bytom, Miscellaneous, EC-0502, 2003-2004 (Box 108, Folder 1179)
  - OhioDance, B-0667, 2006-2009 (Box 108, Folder 1180)
  - OhioDance, DF-0615, 2006-2009 (Box 108, Folder 1181)
  - OhioDance, B-0767, 2007-2009 (Box 108, Folder 1182)
  - Eugene O'Neill Theater Center, EC-0102, 2000-2002, 2006 (Box 108, Folder 1183)
  - Other Minds, DF-0837, 2008-2009 (Box 108, Folder 1184)
  - Outpost for Contemporary Art, B-0628, 2004-2008 (Box 108, Folder 1185)
  - Outpost for Contemporary Art, B-0628, Outpost for Contemporary Art, Kiev and Zagreb Images (Box 108, Folder 1185)
  - Outpost for Contemporary Art, DF-0704, 2006-2007 (Box 108, Folder 1186)
  - Outpost for Contemporary Art, DF-0747, 2007-2009 (Box 108, Folder 1187)
  - P.S. 1 Contemporary Art Center, DF-0112, 2001, 2003 (Box 108, Folder 1188)
  - P.S. 1 Contemporary Art Center, DF-0521, 2004-2006 (Box 108, Folder 1189)
  - P.S. 1 Contemporary Art Center, DF-0521, P.S. 1, Work Samples (Box 108, Folder 1189)
  - Pacific Environment, B-0174, 2001-2003 (Box 109, Folder 1190)
  - Pacific Environment, Miscellaneous, B-0174, 2000-2001 (Box 109, Folder 1191)
  - Pacific Environment, B-0267, 2002-2003 (Box 109, Folder 1192)
  - Pacific Environment, B-0338, 2003-2005 (Box 109, Folder 1193)
  - Pacific Environment, B-0442, 2003-2006 (Box 109, Folder 1194)
  - Pacific Environment, B-0535, 2004-2006 (Box 109, Folder 1195)
  - Pacific Environment, B-0643, 2006-2009 (Box 109, Folder 1196)
  - Pacific Environment, B-0884, 2008-2009 (Box 109, Folder 1197)
  - Palissimo Dance Theatre, B-0518, 2004-2006 (Box 109, Folder 1198)
  - Palissimo Dance Theatre, B-0518, Palissimo, Apostrof, Prague, 2005 (Box 109, Folder 1198)
  - Palissimo Dance Theatre, B-0729, 2005-2009 (Box 109, Folder 1199)
  - Palissimo Dance Theatre, B-0729, Palissimo, 2007 (Box 109, Folder 1199)
  - Parsons Dance Company, B-0730, 2007-2008 (Box 110, Folder 1200)
  - Pasadena Orchestra, EC-0322, 2003, 2005-2007 (Box 110, Folder 1201)
  - Paul Dresher Ensemble, B-0210, DF-0308, 2001-2003 (Box 110, Folder 1202)
  - Paul Dresher Ensemble, B-0210, DF-0308, Paul Dresher Ensemble, Wired Strings Festival, Photos (Box 110, Folder 1202)
  - Paul Dresher Ensemble, the wondergroup, DF-0316, 2003, 2006-2007 (Box 110, Folder 1203)
  - Paul Taylor Dance Company, EC-0615, 2006, 2008 (Box 110, Folder 1204)
  - Peregrine Fund, B-0175, 2001-2002 (Box 110, Folder 1205)
  - Peregrine Fund, B-0268, 2002-2003 (Box 110, Folder 1206)
  - Peregrine Fund, EC-0323, 2003-2004 (Box 110, Folder 1207)
  - Peregrine Fund, EC-0323, The Peregrine Fund, Photos from Mongolia, 2004 November (Box 110, Folder 1207)
  - Performance Space 122, DF-0109, 2001-2002, 2006-2007 (Box 110, Folder 1208)
  - Performance Space 122, DF-02535, 2002-2003, 2006-2007 (Box 110, Folder 1209)
  - Performance Space 122, B-0768, 2005, 2007-2010 (Box 110, Folder 1210)
  - Performance Space 122, B-0768, Women Dreamt Horses, Jay Scheib, Bait, Buenos Aires in Translation, PS 122, NYC, 2006 November (Box 110, Folder 1210)
  - Performance Space 122, B-0768, The Power of Darkness After the Play by Leo Tolstoy, Pont Szinhaz, Budapest, Hungary, 2005 (Box 110, Folder 1210)
  - Performance Space 122, EC-0706, 2005-2007, 2009-2010 (Box 110, Folder 1211)
  - Perspectives of New Music, DF-0633, 2006-2007 (Box 110, Folder 1212)
  - Perspectives of New Music, DF-0633, Perspectives of New Music, Photos, TMU Open Space/PAFME, 2006 December 15-17 (Box 110, Folder 1212)
  - Philadelphia Dance Company, PHILADNACO, B-0136, 1999-2001 (Box 110, Folder 1213)
  - Philadelphia Dance Company, PHILADANCO, B-0769, 2005-2008 (Box 111, Folder 1214)
  - Philadelphia Dance Company, PHILADANCO, Miscellaneous, B-0769, 2008 (Box 111, Folder 1215)
  - Philadelphia Dance Company, PHILADANCO, Miscellaneous, B-0769, Philadance "Blue", Theater der Stadt Schweinfurt, 2008 February 28 (Box 111, Folder 1215)
  - Philadelphia Fringe Festival, B-0137, 1998-2001, 2006-2007 (Box 111, Folder 1216)
  - Philadelphia Fringe Festival, B-0235, 1996-1999, 2002, 2006-2007 (Box 111, Folder 1217)
  - Philadelphia Fringe Festival & Philadelphia Live Arts Festival, B-0731, 2006-2008 (Box 111, Folder 1218)
  - Photo Americas, B-0293, 2002-2003, 2007 (Box 111, Folder 1219)
  - Photographic Resource Center at Boston University, DF-0705, 2006-2009 (Box 111, Folder 1220)
  - Photographic Resource Center at Boston University, DF-0705, PPHB Power Point, "Made in Poland: Contemporary Pinhole Photography", 2007 (Box 111, Folder 1220)
  - Photographic Resource Center at Boston University, DF-0705, PPHB Event Files All "Made in Poland" all Grant Images (Box 111, Folder 1220)
  - Photographic Resource Center at Boston University, DF-0705, PPHB Event Photographs Categories "Made in Poland", 2007 (Box 111, Folder 1220)
  - Pig Iron Theatre Company, B-0138, 2000-2002 (Box 111, Folder 1221)
  - Pig Iron Theatre Company, B-0212, 1970, 1996, 2001-2003, 2005 (Box 111, Folder 1222)
  - Pig Iron Theatre Company, B-0629, 2004-2007 (Box 111, Folder 1223)
  - Pilobolus Dance Theater, B-0829, 2008 (Box 112, Folder 1224)
  - The Play Company, DF-0509, 2003-2005 (Box 112, Folder 1225)
  - The Play Company, DF-0625, 2006, 2008 (Box 112, Folder 1226)
  - The Pond, B-0309, 2002-2005 (Box 112, Folder 1227)
  - The Pond, B-0408, 2002-2005, 2007-2008 (Box 112, Folder 1228)
  - The Pond, DF-0439, 2004-2005, 2007-2008 (Box 112, Folder 1229)
  - The Pond (aka Big & Lil Marsh), DF-0522, 2005, 2007-2008 (Box 112, Folder 1230)
  - The Pond, B-0630, 2005-2008 (Box 112, Folder 1231)
  - The Pond, Miscellaneous, B-0630, 2004, 2006 (Box 112, Folder 1233)
  - The Pond, DF-0830, 2008-2009 (Box 112, Folder 1233)
  - Portland Center Stage, B-0157, 2001-2004, 2006 (Box 112, Folder 1234)
  - Portland Center Stage, B-0157, Portland Center Stage, Merchant of Venice, Images (Box 112, Folder 1234)
  - Portland Khabarovsk Sister City Association, B-0644, 2006-2008 (Box 112, Folder 1235)
  - Portland State University, DF-0204, 1997, 2001-2002 (Box 112, Folder 1236)
  - Preservation Alumni, DF-0217, 2000-2004 (Box 113, Folder 1237)
  - Pro-Cultura, DF-0321, 2002-2004, 2006-2007 (Box 113, Folder 1238)
  - Proto-Type Theater, DF-0341, 2001-2004 (Box 113, Folder 1239)
  - Proto-Type Theater, DF-0341, Proto-Type Theater, Inc., Three Ring, Romania, Photos (Box 113, Folder 1239)
  - Provisions Learning Project, B-0661, 2006-2010 (Box 113, Folder 1240)
  - Quebec-Labrador Foundation, B-02107, 2002-2004, 2007-2008 (Box 113, Folder 1241)
  - Quebec-Labrador Foundation, Miscellaneous, B-02107, 2002 (Box 113, Folder 1242)
  - Quebec-Labrador Foundation, B-0476, 2004-2008 (Box 113, Folder 1243)
  - Quebec-Labrador Foundation, Miscellaneous, B-0476, 2001, 2003, 2005 (Box 113, Folder 1244)
  - Quebec-Labrador Foundation, B-0579, 2005-2008 (Box 114, Folder 1245)
  - Quebec-Labrador Foundation, B-0675, 2006-2008 (Box 114, Folder 1246)
  - Quebec-Labrador Foundation, Miscellaneous, B-0675, 2006-2008 (Box 114, Folder 1247)
  - Quebec-Labrador Foundation, B-0779, 2007-2009 (Box 114, Folder 1248)
  - Quebec Labrador Foundation, B-0885, 2008-2010 (Box 114, Folder 1249)
  - Quebec Labrador Foundation, Miscellaneous, B-0885, 2007 (Box 114, Folder 1250)
  - Quintet of the Americas, B-0254, 2002-2003 (Box 114, Folder 1251)
  - Rails to Trails Conservancy, B-0111, 2000-2002 (Box 114, Folder 1252)
  - Rails to Trails Conservancy, B-0218, 2001-2004 (Box 114, Folder 1253)
  - Rails to Trails Conservancy, B-0218, International Pictures from TrailLink 2003 (Box 114, Folder 1253)
  - Ramapo College, B-0231, 2002-2003, 2005 (Box 115, Folder 1254)
  - Real Art Ways, DF-0631, 2006-2007 (Box 115, Folder 1255)
  - Real Art Ways, DF-0631, Real Art Ways, "Poza" Exhibition, Images (Box 115, Folder 1255)
  - Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute, DF-0205, 2001-2004, 2006-2007 (Box 115, Folder 1256)
  - The Research Foundation of SUNY: The Cuban Research Institute, B-0812, 2004, 2008-2009 (Box 115, Folder 1257)
  - The Research Foundation of SUNY: The Cuban Research Institute, B-0812, Future of the Arts in Cuba Conference, 2009 April (Box 115, Folder 1257)
  - Rhizome.org, Art Services Unlimited 2, DF-0129, 1999-2002 (Box 115, Folder 1258)
  - Risa Jaroslow & Dancers, B-0207, 2001-2002, 2006-2007 (Box 115, Folder 1259)
  - Risa Jaroslow & Dancers, High Tide Dance Inc., B-0294, 2002-2003, 2006-2007 (Box 115, Folder 1260)
  - Risa Jaroslow & Dancers, EC-0406, 2003-2004, 2006-2007 (Box 115, Folder 1261)
  - River Arts Repertory Company, EC-0207, 2001-2003, 2006-2007 (Box 115, Folder 1262)
  - River Arts Repertory Company, B-0519, 2003, 2005-2006 (Box 115, Folder 1263)
  - River Arts Repertory Company, B-0519, GV SP Company, Photos (Box 115, Folder 1263)
  - Riverside Ensemble of New Mexico, Ghosts, B-0158, 2000-2003 (Box 115, Folder 1264)
  - Riverside Ensemble of New Mexico, B-0255, 2000, 2002-2003 (Box 116, Folder 1265)
  - The Rubin Museum of Art, DF-0423, 2003-2005 (Box 116, Folder 1266)
  - The Rubin Museum of Art, DF-0534, 2005-2006 (Box 116, Folder 1267)
  - Rubin Museum of Art, Miscellaneous, DF-0534, 2004 (Box 116, Folder 1268)
  - Rubin Museum of Art, Miscellaneous, B-0534, Rubin Museum of Art, Chirgilchin, 2005 November 4 (Box 116, Folder 1268)
  - Rubin Museum of Art, Miscellaneous, B-0534, Rubin Museum of Art, Songs of the Steppes, 2005 November 11 (Box 116, Folder 1268)
  - Russian-American Cultural Center, DF-0723, 2006-2008 (Box 116, Folder 1269)
  - Russian National Orchestra, Russian Arts Foundation, B-0159, 1997, 1999-2004 (Box 116, Folder 1270)
  - Russian National Orchestra, DF-0440, 2003-2006 (Box 116, Folder 1271)
  - Russian National Orchestra, DF-0722, 2005, 2007, 2009 (Box 116, Folder 1272)
  - Russian National Orchestra, Russian Arts Foundation, Miscellaneous, DF-0722, 2005 (Box 116, Folder 1273)
  - Rutgers University, Zimmerli Art Museum, DF-9776, B-9947, DF-0334, 1997-2003 (Box 116, Folder 1274)
  - Sacred Earth Network, B-0112, 1999, 2001-2002 (Box 116, Folder 1275)
  - Sacred Earth Network, B-02109, 2001-2005 (Box 116, Folder 1276)
  - Sacred Earth Network, B-0545, 2001, 2004-2008 (Box 116, Folder 1277)
  - Sacred Earth Network, B-0545, Sacred Earth Network, Siberia, 2006 June; CD-R (Box 116, Folder 1277)
  - Sacred Earth Network, B-0545, Sacred Earth Network, U.S. Southwest, 2006 October-November (Box 116, Folder 1277)
  - Sacred Earth Network, DF-0635, 2006-2007, 2009 (Box 116, Folder 1278)
  - St. Ann Center for Restoration and the Arts, DF-0431, 2004-2005 (Box 116, Folder 1279)
  - St. Ann Center for Restoration and the Arts, B-0607, 2002, 2004-2008 (Box 117, Folder 1280)
  - St. Ann Center for Restoration and the Arts, EC-0701, 2006-2008 (Box 117, Folder 1281)
  - Salzburg Seminar, EC-0105, 2001-2002, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 1282)
  - San Diego State University, B-0520, 2004-2007 (Box 117, Folder 1283)
  - San Francisco International Arts Festival, B-0732, 2006-2009 (Box 117, Folder 1284)
  - San Francisco International Arts Festival, B-0830, 2007-2009 (Box 117, Folder 1285)
  - Sandglass Theater, DF-0104, 2000-2002 (Box 117, Folder 1286)
  - Santa Fe Art Institute, B-0566, 2002, 2004-2007 (Box 117, Folder 1287)
  - Santa Fe Art Institute, B-0566, Santa Fe Art Institute, TMU Images (Box 117, Folder 1287)
  - Santa Fe Art Institute, Miscellaneous, B-0566, 2006 (Box 117, Folder 1288)
  - Santa Fe Art Institute, Miscellaneous, Palestina, 6:30 min, Alban Muja, 2005 (Box 117, Folder 1288)
  - Santa Fe Art Institute, Miscellaneous, Tomas Hlavina, Aida Sehovic, Images of Work Completed/In Progress During Time at SFAI (Box 117, Folder 1288)
  - Santa Fe Art Institute, B-0668, 2004-2008 (Box 117, Folder 1289)
  - Santa Fe Art Institute, B-0668, Santa Fe Art Institute, TMU 2007 Residency (Box 117, Folder 1289)
  - The School of Hard Knocks, B-01102, 2001-2002, 2007 (Box 118, Folder 1290)
  - The School of Hard Knocks, B-0567, 2005-2006, 2008 (Box 118, Folder 1291)
  - The School of Hard Knocks, DF-0531, 2005-2006 (Box 118, Folder 1292)
  - The Science Project, EC-0208, 2002-2004 (Box 118, Folder 1293)
  - SculptureCenter, Spaces of Femininity, EC-0209, 2001-2003, 2007 (Box 118, Folder 1294)
  - SculptureCenter, Spaces of Femininity, EC-0209, SculptureCenter, Images from Architectures of Gender: Contemporary Women's Art in Poland, 2003 (Box 118, Folder 1294)
  - Seagull Films International, B-0872, 2000-2004, 2006, 2008-2010 (Box 118, Folder 1295)
  - Seattle Chamber Players, B-01103, 1999-2002 (Box 118, Folder 1296)
  - Seattle Chamber Players, B-0325, 2002-2004, 2007 (Box 118, Folder 1297)
  - Seattle Chamber Players, B-0521, 2003-2006, 2008 (Box 118, Folder 1298)
  - Seattle Chamber Players, EC-0808, 2004, 2008 (Box 118, Folder 1299)
  - The Seeds Project, B-0780, 2002, 2007-2009 (Box 118, Folder 1300)
  - S.E.M. Ensemble, B-0295, 2002-2003 (Box 118, Folder 1301)
  - S.E.M. Ensemble, B-0295, Ostrava Days, 2003, Photographs (Box 118, Folder 1301)
  - S.E.M. Ensemble, B-0342 (Cancelled), 2002-2005 (Box 118, Folder 1302)
  - S.E.M. Ensemble, B-0468, 2003-2006 (Box 119, Folder 1303)
  - S.E.M. Ensemble B-0468, SEM Ensemble, Ostrava Days, Czech Republic, Photos, 2005 August (Box 119, Folder 1303)
  - S.E.M. Ensemble, Ostrava Days 2005, Miscellaneous, B-0468, 2003, 2005 (Box 119, Folder 1304)
  - S.E.M. Ensemble, DF-0626, 2005-2007 (Box 119, Folder 1305)
  - S.E.M. Ensemble, DF-0626, Ostravska Banda, 2006 European Tour, 2006 October 23-November 8 (Box 119, Folder 1305)
  - S.E.M. Ensemble, DF-0626, Ostrava Days 2005, Report (Box 119, Folder 1305)
  - S.E.M. Ensemble, Ostrava Days 2007, B-0733, 2006-2008 (Box 119, Folder 1306)
  - S.E.M. Ensemble, Ostrava Days 2007, B-0733, SEM Ensemble, Photos Ostrava Days for TMU (Box 119, Folder 1306)
  - S.E.M. Ensemble, Ostrava Days 2007, Miscellaneous, B-0733 (Box 119, Folder 1307)
  - Seven Stages, B-0213, 2001-2003 (Box 119, Folder 1308)
  - Seven Stages, EC-0404, 2002-2005 (Box 119, Folder 1309)
  - Seven Stages, B-0522, 2004-2005, 2008 (Box 119, Folder 1310)
  - Shen Wei Dance Arts, B-0770, 2007-2009 (Box 119, Folder 1311)
  - Shen Wei Dance Arts, B-0770, Shen Wei Dance Arts, Budapest Hungary, Performance Photographs Folding, 2008 (Box 119, Folder 1311)
  - Shen Wei Dance Arts, B-0771, Shen Wei Dance Arts, Excerpts from: Rite of Spring, Folding, Connect Transfer, Oil Paintings by Shen Wei, Rite of Spring, Near the Terracem Second Visit to the Empress, Map, 2007 (Box 119, Folder 1311)
  - Shen Wei Dance Arts, Miscellaneous, B-0770, 2006-2008 (Box 119, Folder 1312)
  - SITI Company, DF-0717, 2007-2008 (Box 120, Folder 1313)
  - Sixth World Symposium of Choral Music, B-0160, 2001-2003 (Box 120, Folder 1314)
  - Skewed Visions Performance, DF-0724, 2007-2008 (Box 120, Folder 1315)
  - Smithsonian Institution, B-01104, 2001-2003, 2005 (Box 120, Folder 1316)
  - Smithsonian Institution, Center for Folklife Programs and Cultural Studies, Miscellaneous, B-01104, 2002 (Box 120, Folder 1318)
  - Smithsonian Institution, Cooper-Hewitt National Design Center, DF-0105, 2000-2003, 2007 (Box 120, Folder 1318)
  - Smithsonian Institution, DF-0330, 2003-2004, 2006-2007 (Box 120, Folder 1319)
  - Smithsonian Institution, DF-0330, National Museum of Natural History, TMU, Bill Fitzhugh Images, Mongolia Deerstone Project, 2003 (Box 120, Folder 1319)
  - Smithsonian Institution, EC-0410, 2004-2006 (Box 120, Folder 1320)
  - Smithsonian Institution, EC-0410, Smithsonian, Mongolia Deerstone Project, 2004 (Box 120, Folder 1320)
  - Smithsonian Institution, National Museum of Natural History, B-0523, 2005-2006 (Box 120, Folder 1321)
  - Smithsonian Institution, B-0632, 2005-2007 (Box 120, Folder 1322)
  - Smithsonian Institution, B-0632, Smithsonian, William Fitzhugh, Fieldwork in Mongolia, Photographs for TMU (Box 120, Folder 1322)
  - Smithsonian Institution, B-0734, 2006-2008 (Box 120, Folder 1323)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Freer Gallery of Art and Sackler Gallery, DF-0826, 2007-2009 (Box 120, Folder 1324)
  - Snug Harbor, DF-0220, 2000, 2002-2003, 2007 (Box 120, Folder 1326)
  - Society for Ecological Restoration, B-0113, 2000-2003, 2007 (Box 121, Folder 1326)
  - Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum, B-0524, 2002, 2004-2006 (Box 121, Folder 1327)
  - SoundArt Foundation, DF-0116, 1975, 1978, 1982, 1988, 1995-1996, 1998-2003 (Box 121, Folder 1328)